Everybody knows I make social media
videos, but this is not me making a
video. This is just me talking y'all,
letting you know what's going on in my
life actually with no cuts, no edits.
I've been working like a dog in Costa
Rica. I built an entire room full of
solar panels in Black Hawk and I took my
finca off-grid. I fixed the broken
manguera pipe. I've been building this
little love nest with Alex in the back
with nothing but a DeWalt combo. I've
learned Spanish. He aprendido español
con pronto amigo and I'm trying to kind
of, you know, assimilate to the Costa
Rican lifestyle which is hard because it
moves so slow.
There's lovely Alex there. What's going
on in our life, Evan?
>> Mhm.
Mhm. Building stuff.
>> Has it been easy?
>> No.
>> Has this not been the hardest 12 months
of our life?
>> Absolutely.
>> Do we get a lot of bad for all the good
we put out in the world?
>> More so, yeah.
>> What do you think the problem is?
>> I'd say the problem is us.
>> How can we do anything different or
better?
>> Uh
lower our standards.
>> I can't do that.
>> No.
>> I do hold myself to high standards, you
know, I think there's a basic level that
people need to meet for themselves and
if you look at the world right now, they
ain't meeting it. The world is consumed
with violence right now and there are
people dying all over planet Earth. You
know, women and children and civilians,
non-combatants. They're people just like
me and you. They're just They're just in
different countries and they're being
blown up and obliterated, bridges and
hospitals and schools
and all people are worried about is the
price of gas.
Where is our humanity gone?
I mean, look at the leader of America
right now. On Easter Sunday, the things
coming out of his mouth. You know, when
it it just breaks my heart that, you
know, people who rise to a position of
power use it for such a bad thing and I
understand that, you know, a lot of
people see the things I put online now
and listen to what I have to say and I'm
doing the best I can to put a good
positive message out there to let you
know that you can chase your dreams. You
can do something better than you were
doing before, but boy, it is a heavy
load and a long tough road. But, I just
wanted to give you a little update on
Easter Sunday to let you know that Joe
and Alex is still in here. We are still
striving. We are still grinding. God
loves you and so do I. Happy Easter. He
is risen for sure.